<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<VFET.AvailableCornerstonePoint>Available cornerstone point</VFET.AvailableCornerstonePoint>
	<VFET.AvailableCornerstonePoints>Available cornerstone points: {0}</VFET.AvailableCornerstonePoints>
	<VFET.AvailableCornerstonePointDesc>You can spend a cornerstone point to gain a permanent, colony-wide buff that will help you shape your civilization.</VFET.AvailableCornerstonePointDesc>
	<VFET.Cornerstones>Cornerstones</VFET.Cornerstones>
	<VFET.CustomizeCornerstones>Customize cornerstones</VFET.CustomizeCornerstones>
	<VFET.Ethos>Ethos</VFET.Ethos>
	<VFET.EthosUnlocked>Lock or unlock the faction's ethos. When locked, the ethos text will not auto-regenerate when you unlock a new cornerstone.

Ethos lock is currently off. The ethos text can auto-regenerate.</VFET.EthosUnlocked>
	<VFET.EthosLocked>Lock or unlock the faction's ethos. When locked, the ethos text will not auto-regenerate when you unlock a new cornerstone.

Ethos lock is currently on. The ethos text will not auto-regenerate.</VFET.EthosLocked>
	<VFET.CornerstonesExplanation>Gain cornerstone points by advancing to next tech levels</VFET.CornerstonesExplanation>
	<VFET.EthosTooltip>The core ethos of your faction. This text has no gameplay impact, but associated cornerstones do.</VFET.EthosTooltip>
	<VFET.EditEthos>Edit ethos</VFET.EditEthos>
	<VFET.UnlockCornerstone>Unlock cornerstone</VFET.UnlockCornerstone>
	<VFET.StatsReport_Cornerstones>Relevant cornerstones</VFET.StatsReport_Cornerstones>
	<VFET.WorkDisabledByMissingResearch>Research {0} to unlock it</VFET.WorkDisabledByMissingResearch>
	<VFET.FormIdeology>Form ideology</VFET.FormIdeology>
	<VFET.FormIdeologyDesc>What should your colonists believe? These beliefs affect gameplay and visuals. You will be able to recruit others to your beliefs, or take on their beliefs.\n\n
Choosing classic will allow you to play without the ideology system. All Ideology expansion content remains active.\n\n
Choosing fluid will allow you to start with a basic ideology and develop it over time.\n\n
Choosing fixed allows you to customize the ideology and every aspect of it. This may take some time.</VFET.FormIdeologyDesc>
	<VFET.WildMenJoin>Due to the small number of wild men, they have decided to join you.</VFET.WildMenJoin>
	<VFET.WildMenRetreat>Due to the uncertainty of being able to best you, wild men have decided to retreat.</VFET.WildMenRetreat>
	<VFET.WildMenJoinTitle>Wild men ask to join</VFET.WildMenJoinTitle>
	<VFET.WildMenJoinDesc>Wild men from the nearby tribe found their way to {0}. After seeing your numbers, they are requesting to join you. They believe that together, you stand a better chance against the elements.\n\nYou can refuse them, but they may retaliate as a result.</VFET.WildMenJoinDesc>
	<VFET.WildMenRaid>Wild men raid</VFET.WildMenRaid>
	<VFET.WildMenRaidDesc>Wild men from the nearby tribe found their way to {0}. After seeing your numbers, they have decided to raid you. You might be able to capture and recruit any survivors.</VFET.WildMenRaidDesc>
	<VFET.Reject>Reject</VFET.Reject>
	<VFET.WorkTypeName>{0} work type</VFET.WorkTypeName>
	<VFET_WildmanLetterLabel>Wild man joins</VFET_WildmanLetterLabel>
	<VFET_WildmanLetter>A wild man wanders in and decides to join your colony</VFET_WildmanLetter>
	<VFET_AnimalsLetterLabel>Farm animals wander in</VFET_AnimalsLetterLabel>
	<VFET_AnimalsLetter>A group of farm animals has been attracted and will join the colony</VFET_AnimalsLetter>
	<VFET_DiscoveryLabel>Discovered {0}!</VFET_DiscoveryLabel>
	<VFET_Discovery>A new research project has been discovered in a tribal gathering: {0}!\n\n{1}</VFET_Discovery>
	<VFET.AnimalTrapSprung>Animal trap has sprung on {0}</VFET.AnimalTrapSprung>
	<VFET.LightLargeFire>Light large fire</VFET.LightLargeFire>
	<VFET.ExtinguishLargeFire>Extinguish large fire</VFET.ExtinguishLargeFire>
	<VFET.LightLargeFireDesc>When burning, large fire emits blindsmoke and has a chance to encourage wild men from the local area to wander in. It's very unstable and may set things around it on fire.</VFET.LightLargeFireDesc>
	<VFET.ResearchLeft_Neolithic>Some Animal tech research must still be completed.</VFET.ResearchLeft_Neolithic>
	
	<!--These are needed for Ideology compat -->
	
	<Optional>optional</Optional>
	<RitualTargetGatherSpotInfo>Any gathering spot, like a table</RitualTargetGatherSpotInfo>
	
	<VFET.MustPlaceOnFloorOrStonyTerrain>Must be placed on a floor or stony terrain.</VFET.MustPlaceOnFloorOrStonyTerrain>
</LanguageData>