<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
	<defName>VFET_FormTribe</defName>
	<label>Neolithic tech level</label>
	<description>You have sucessfully completed all pre-neolithic research projects and have advanced to neolithic tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization.</description>
	<newTechLevel>Neolithic</newTechLevel>
	<cornerstonePoint>1</cornerstonePoint>
  </VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>

  <VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
	<defName>VFET_FormTown</defName>
	<label>Medieval tech level</label>
	<description>You have sucessfully completed all neolithic research projects and have advanced to medieval tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization.</description>
	<newTechLevel>Medieval</newTechLevel>
	<cornerstonePoint>1</cornerstonePoint>
  </VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>

  <VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
	<defName>VFET_FormCity</defName>
	<label>Industrial tech level</label>
	<description>You have sucessfully completed all medieval research projects and have advanced to industrial tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization.</description>
	<newTechLevel>Industrial</newTechLevel>
	<cornerstonePoint>1</cornerstonePoint>
  </VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
  
  <VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
	<defName>VFET_FormCollective</defName>
	<label>Spacer tech level</label>
	<description>You have sucessfully completed all industrial research projects and have advanced to spacer tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization.</description>
	<newTechLevel>Spacer</newTechLevel>
	<cornerstonePoint>1</cornerstonePoint>
  </VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
  
  <VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
	<defName>VFET_FormNexus</defName>
	<label>Ultratech tech level</label>
	<description>You have sucessfully completed all spacer research projects and have advanced to ultratech tech level. This will allow you to pick a Cornerstone - a powerful bonus that applies only to your civilization.</description>
	<newTechLevel>Ultra</newTechLevel>
	<cornerstonePoint>1</cornerstonePoint>
  </VFETribals.EraAdvancementDef>
  
</Defs>
